Panu Robert Niskakoski

Technical Game Artist & Generalist

CONTACT







LinkedIn

Online Portfolio

My Website

ABOUT ME



For the past 4 years, I've worked as a game artist and a generalist at Unibyte Studios. I have plenty of experience in creating 2D graphics & animation, sound production (SFX / MUSIC) as well as game programming. I am also a novice 3D artist.

I have a master's degree in IT from the University of Jyväskylä. In my studies, I focused on game development.

I've done freelance graphic design gigs varying from band shirts to deck designs and from company logos to social media creatives.

Ö

DEV TOOLS



Procreate & Gimp

Unity

Blender

Aseprite

Reaper & Audacity

Trello & Asana

Game Maker Studio

Github Desktop

PROGRAMMING

C#

JavaScript

HTML & CSS

lava

LANGUAGES



Finnish

English

Swedish

EDUCATION



◆ MASTER OF SCIENCE (IT) ◆ University of Jyväskylä | 2017 – 2022

Masters thesis about animal-computer interaction (ACI)

♦ NCO-Course ◆

Karjala Brigade | 2013 - 2014

REFERENCES

Will be given upon request.

\equiv

WORK EXPERIENCE



★ CEO & LEAD DESIGNER ★

Herra Koira Company | 2023 – present Game design - Research - Graphics & Animation - Sound design Marketing material - Prototyping - QA

★ GAME ARTIST & GENERALIST ★

Unibyte Studios | 2019 – 2023 2D Graphics - Marketing material - Music & SFX – Testing - Design

★ GRAPHIC DESIGNER ★

Freelance | 2018 - present Company logos - Shirt designs - Social media creatives - Prints **Business charts - Skateboard decks**

★ DEPARTMENT MANAGER ★

K-Supermarket Kotikenttä | 2014 – 2017 Orders - Campaigns - Loss tracking – Inventory - Negotiations

